Jayme Hewitt

4033 NE 197th St · Lake Forest Park, WA 98155 (310) 717-5381 · jaymeahewitt@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/jaymehewitt

November 2, 2018

Hi there!

I recently spoke with Sreekanth Veerapandian about his experience working at Expedia Group. It sounds like an exciting, supportive environment that is making the world a smaller place. The traveler in me loves that.

As a team player who trusts in user-centered product development I believe I would thrive as a product manager with your teams. I love working with customers to define problems they are having, bringing those problems into light on a roadmap, and discovering solutions with designers and engineers to bring value to the business and satisfaction to the customer. I am:

• Passionate about user feedback

While working in customer service at my last company I discovered that no customer feedback program existed. I immediately asked to change roles and develop a feedback loop to bring the customer voice into product development.

• Constantly seeking to learn and evolve

I devour product blogs, have workshopped with Teresa Torres and C Todd Lombardo at the Mind the Product conference, and enjoyed working with a private team product coach while at Geocaching HQ.

• A collaborative, communicative team player

I have led 8 product launches, including the successful re-launch of the geocaching.com user dashboard with a 72% customer adoption rate.

Please see my attached resume for more details on my experience.

As an avid traveler (with kids in tow) I appreciate your guiding principle of putting yourself in the shoes of the customer/partner. Empathy creates understanding, and being well understood by the company you just made all your travel plans with can make or break your experience. Employing technology to make traveling easier than expected, delights customers. I would love to share my customer-centric, product-minded skills with the talented community of Expedia Group to woo current and future adventurers.

Thank you for creating a company with a heart of kindness that gives back to the world. I'd love the opportunity to chat more.

Jayme Hewitt

Jayme Hewitt

4033 NE 197th St · Lake Forest Park, WA 98155

(310) 717-5381 · jaymeahewitt@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/jaymehewitt

EXPERIENCE

Mom (April 2018 – Current)

As a Mom of two kids under four, I am able to bond with my kids and nurture the next generation of independent thinkers, while further developing some of the soft skills used in day-to-day product management. Some of these skills include:

- Active listening
- Time management
- Monitoring
- Complex problem solving
- Critical thinking
- Empathy

Geocaching HQ | Seattle, Washington

Product Manager (April 2016 – April 2018)

As a Product Manager I work closely with a Product Designer, Lead Website Developer, and the Geocaching community to bring helpful and innovative changes to the Geocaching website. Some of my responsibilities include:

- Prioritizing the work to be done based on user needs, business requirements, and development resources available.
- Interviewing users to learn more about the needs and desires of the community that uses the website.
- Listening to internal stakeholders to better understand the specific needs of the team requesting a new feature.
- Story mapping to fully understand what currently exists, why it exists, and the ramifications of making any changes.
- Teaming with a Product Designer to understand the customer journey and open the funnel: from understanding the game (homepage) to finding/logging a geocache (target behavior) to premium membership purchase (business needs).
- Helping to establish a company roadmap, based on company OKR's, and proposing solutions to meet those goals.
- Partnering with the Data team to determine baseline metrics for measuring product effectiveness
- Pairing with a Dev Lead, creating stories/bugs and moving them through a delivery team's backlog to completion.
- Gaining a qualitative understanding of user pain points and satisfaction of a new features through iterative releases.
- Helping to QA work before and after a release.
- Creating and communicating a product release strategy with the Community Engagement and Marketing teams.
- Participating in company-wide demonstrations of the delivery team's work.

Geocaching HQ | Seattle, Washington

User Insights Analyst (June 2014 – April 2016)

As a User Insight Analyst, on the Product team, I developed a user feedback program that helped provide direction for the development of features on the Geocaching website and app. Some of my responsibilities include:

- Engaging with the community in user insight forums to gain a qualitative understanding of how they use our site.
- Gaining insight into usage on current features and satisfaction of newly released features through surveys.
- Creating and facilitating focus groups using Innovation Games. (Germany, Sweden, Czech Republic, Spain, and USA)
- Creating and running a worldwide Play Tester program in order to receive feedback quickly on new features.
- Analyzing and compiling qualitative results into recommendations that represent the voice of the community.
- Passing the knowledge gained onto the Product team, Sr. Management team, and Marketing teams to influence product design, roadmap, and feature decisions.

Geocaching HQ | Seattle, Washington

Community Volunteer Support Coordinator (May 2013 – June 2014)

As a Coordinator on the Community Volunteer Support team I engage daily with a group of ~400 passionate, dedicated geocaching community members who volunteer their time. Some of my responsibilities include:

- Answering questions and dispute resolution between general community members and volunteer geocache reviewers.
- Supporting the volunteer forum moderators as the main geocaching representative in the public forums.

- Re-establishing trust with the geocaching community through daily engagement in the public forums.
- Creating a safer environment for new players to ask questions and engage with the existing community in the forums.
- Assisting in implementation of an auto-responder feature in the Help Center in order to offer clear answers to common, general questions to the community and to reduce the amount of help requests for the Community team.

United States Postal Service | Enumclaw, Washington

Rural Carrier Associate (June 2012 – May 2013)

As a carrier, I sort, deliver, and collect mail along a prescribed rural route and provide customers on the route with fantastic customer service. My responsibilities include:

- Sorting mail in delivery sequence for the assigned route
- Receiving and signing for accountable mail (express, registered, COD)
- Returning mail collected, undeliverable mail, and submitting monies and receipts to post office
- Preparing mail for forwarding and maintaining records of change of address information
- Providing for mail security at all times

Enumclaw Self Storage | Enumclaw, Washington

Front Office Staff (June 2011 – May 2012, June 1999 – September 2001)

As part of a team of front desk staff, my responsibilities included:

- Fielding phone and in person questions regarding storage and moving truck rentals
- Showing and renting units and moving trucks to customers
- Accepting and processing in person, phone, and online customer payments
- Completing pre-lien and lien processes in accordance with state laws
- Helping delinquent tenants return to on-time payments
- Tracking inventory of moving supply products
- Assembling bank deposits and reconciling petty cash
- Maintaining a secure, clean facility

Stunts Unlimited | Los Angeles, California

Office Manager (September 2001 – May 2011)

Assisted members of Hollywood's top stunt organization in their various production schedules as well as managed all aspects of the day-to-day operations of the busy office, including:

- Handling all member, production company, and customer contacts and communication
- Updating resumes for members and referring incoming work calls to the appropriately skilled stunt coordinator
- Maintaining the office space and organizing monthly meetings for fifty coordinators
- Finding talent and setting up auditions for various TV and film stunt jobs
- Ordering, stocking, and selling merchandise in store and online
- Administering the online store and website
- Reconciling merchandise sales with cash on hand

Actress/Stunt Performer (September 1999 – May 2011)

Credited and uncredited roles on a variety of TV/film productions, including Takers, CSI: New York (5 episodes), Lie to Me, 24, Meet Dave, Evan Almighty, The 40 Year Old Virgin, The Princess Diaries 2: The Royal Engagement, The Haunted Mansion, and Rose Red

• Credits viewable on www.imdb.com under professional name of Jayme Jensen

EDUCATION

Brenneke School of Massage, Licensed Massage Practitioner (September 1999 – June 2000)

Western Washington University, Undergraduate Coursework (September 1997 – June 1999)

• 3.5 GPA in psychology curriculum

Enumclaw High School, Honors Graduate (September 1993 – June 1997)

- 3.8 GPA including multiple AP and college-credit courses
- Studied German for four years, including three week exchange program near Munich